Vose Galleries of Boston
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1895-1996, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-23; 22.6 linear feet)
  - Hurd, L.R., 1924-1925 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Hutchinson & Company, 1921-1924 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - I File, 1925-1939, 1947, 1993, (4 folders) (Box 8, Folder 29-32)
  - Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1971-1979 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Inquiries, 1921-1929, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 34-35)
  - International Studio, 1929, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Interoffice, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - J File, 1919-1940, 1947, 1993, (4 folders) (Box 8, Folder 38-41)
  - Jacklin and Company, 1972-1979 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Jackman, Howard, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Jackson, Robert, 1929-1930, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Jetté, Ellerton and Edith, 1972-1982 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Job Applicants, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Johnson, Jackson, 1921-1924 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Jones, Paul, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Jonniaux, Alfred, 1963-1964, (2 folders; Arranged in reverse chronological order) (Box 8, Folder 49-50)
  - Jonniaux, Alfred, 1950-1963, (14 folders; Arranged in reverse chronological order) (Box 9, Folder 1-14)
  - Jonniaux, Alfred, Correspondence Regarding Jonniaux, 1948-1951 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Jonniaux, Alfred, Correspondence Regarding Jonniaux Portraits, 1949-1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Jonniaux, Alfred, Regarding Works, A-Z (1956-1958), 1953, 1955-1958, 1960, (14 folders) (Box 10, Folder 3-16)
  - Jonniaux, Alfred, Regarding Works, A-Z (1959), 1953, 1957-1960, (10 folders) (Box 10, Folder 17-26)
  - Jonniaux, Alfred, Regarding Works, A-Z (1960-1961), 1956-1961, (13 folders) (Box 10, Folder 27-39)
  - Joslyn Memorial, 1937-1939, 1947, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - K File, 1921-1940, 1947, 1993, (5 folders) (Box 11, Folder 1-5)
  - Kahler, Carl, 1923, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Kaiser, Dorothea, 1958-1963, 1985, (3 folders) (Box 11, Folder 7-9)
  - The Kansas City Art Institute, 1921-1925, 1929-1930, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
  - [Kansas City, MO] From R.C. Vose, 1929, October (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Kansas City, MO, 1933, 1967-1978, (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 13-14)
  - [The University of Kansas Museum of Art, Lawrence, Kansas], 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Keep, Helen, circa 1936-1939, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Kellogg, Edward B., Mrs., 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Kelsey, Aaron L., 1921-1926 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Kendall Whaling Museum, 1971-1976 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Kennedy & Co., 1920-1925, 1934-1938, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 20-21)
  - Frederick Keppel & Co., 1929, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Coe Kerr Gallery, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Kimball Estate, 1920-1924, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - King, Ralph, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Kingan, Samuel L., 1920-1925 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Kinsman, Edith, 1924-1925, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - F. Kleinberger Galleries, 1922-1939, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 28-29)
  - M. Knoedler & Co., 1928-1938, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 30-31)
  - Koch, Alfred B., 1924 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Koehler, Hugo A., 1929, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Kohler, C.J., Mrs., 1929, 1933, 1938, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Kryl, Bohumir, 1929, 1937, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - L File, 1921-1929, (4 folders) (Box 11, Folder 36-39)
  - L File, 1937-1940, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Ladd, Anna Coleman (Estate of), circa 1920s, 1941-1942, [1977?] (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Larkin, Gerard R., 1920-1924 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Lauriat, Charles E., 1925 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Lavery, John, Sir, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Lawton, Herbert, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Legal, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - J. Leger & Son, Inc., 1928-1929 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Legislation, 1923-1924 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Lemon & Son, 1924-1925 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Lesch, Rudolf, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Letts, Ira Lloyd, 1924-1929, (3 folders) (Box 12, Folder 12-14)
  - Lie Exhibition, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - The H. Lieber Company, 1922-1925, 1929, (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 16-17)
  - Lieber Galleries, 1926, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Liggett, Louis K., 1920-1926, (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 19-20)
  - Lion, Flora, 1925-1926 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Locke, Edwin, Dr., 1926 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Lockwood, L. Vincent, 1925-1926 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Logan, Frank, Mrs., 1935-1937, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Lombard, P.H., 1925 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Long, Breckenridge, Mr. and Mrs., 1921-1929, (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 26-27)
  - Loring, Paul E., 1937, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Los Angeles Art Association, circa 1933-1938, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1975-1980 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Loughlin, J.B., 1921-1925 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - R.H. Love Galleries, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Low, John F., 1927-1929, (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 33-34)
  - Lowry, George [Poultry], 1929 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Lowy, Julius, 1937-1938, 1947, (Contains artwork frame designs) (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Lucioni, Luigi, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - M File, 1915-1941, 1947, 1978, 1993, (9 folders) (Box 12, Folder 38-46)
  - M File, 1934-1947, 1993, (3 folders) (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
  - Macbeth Galleries, 1921-1933, (8 folders) (Box 13, Folder 4-11)
  - Macomber Case, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Macomber, Frank Gair, 1920-1929, 1985, (4 folders) (Box 13, Folder 13-16)
  - Dr. S.N. Maimon, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Malden Public Library (F.A. Shove), 1925, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Malden Public Library, 1926-1928, 1934-1946, (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 19-20)
  - Manchester Institute of Arts and Science, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Manitowac, Wisconsin [Rahr West Museum], 1969-1976 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Margolis Shop, 1928-1929 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - The Mariners Museum, 1972-1980 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Martin, Alec, Sir, 1932-1946 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Martin, Charles J., Mrs., 1923-1924 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Martin, Willard S., 1921-1929 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Mason, Roy, 1938-1946 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Mauran, William L., 1923 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Maxwell Galleries, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Guy Mayer Gallery (Formerly J. George Mayer Art Gallery), 1939-1942 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Mayer, Louis, 1923-1925 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Mayflower Society, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Mazzanovich, Lawrence, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Mc File, 1921-1942, 1947, 1993, (4 folders) (Box 14, Folder 4-7)
  - McCaughen & Burr, 1923, 1974-1978, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
  - McCaulley, Frank D., 1920-1924 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - McClees Galleries, 1925-1929, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 11-12)
  - Dr. Harold McCracken [Whitney Gallery of Western Art], 1966-1979 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - McGirr, Newman F., 1929 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - McGurk, Jonce I., 1921-1925 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - William K. McKay Company, 1921-1924 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - McMillan, J.G., 1923-1925 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - McVitty, Albert E., 1921-1925 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Mechlin, Leila, 1932, 1936-1938 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Melchers, Gari, 1921-1922 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - The Memorial Art Gallery, 1923, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Metropolitan Galleries, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1921-1946, 1966-1979, (5 folders) (Box 14, Folder 23-27)
  - Meyersahm, Exene, 1921-1932 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Mezquita, Lopez, Senor, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Milch Galleries, 1921-1946, (4 folders) (Box 14, Folder 30-33)
  - Millar, Leslie, 1931, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - J.H. Miller Co., 1925-1926 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Miller, Marion M., 1921-1927 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Miller, Otto, 1920-1928, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 37-38)
  - Mills, E.C., 1920-1923 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Milwaukee Art Institute, 1921-1930, (3 folders) (Box 14, Folder 40-42)
  - Miniger, C.O., 1926-1929, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 43-44)
  - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1921-1934, (4 folders) (Box 14, Folder 45-48)
  - Mobile Art Gallery, 1969-1978 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Monif, H. Kahn, 1928, 1931-1932 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Monks, Grace B., 1925 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Monks, J.A.S., Mrs., 1922-1924 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Montreal Art Association, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - The Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, 1965-1975 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Morey, Samuel F., 1921-1922 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Morgan, John Hill, 1935-1943 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Morris, Harrison and Catherine Morris Wright, 1928-1929, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 57-58)
  - Mostyn, Tom, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Mott, Charles Stewart, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Mulhaupt, Frederick and Zonwice, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Muller, G. Frank, 1925-1926 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Muller, Joseph, 1939-1945 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Mundy, Ethel, 1926-1929, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 64-65)
  - Murphy, H. Dudley, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Murphy, J. Francis, Mrs., 1921 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Museum of Fine Arts (Boston, MA), 1926-1938, (See also "Boston Museum of Fine Arts") (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Museums and Art Societies, 1921-1929, 1996, (3 folders) (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
  - N File, 1916-1946, 1993, (5 folders) (Box 15, Folder 4-8)
  - Napton, Suzanne, 1923-1927 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Design, 1925-1927 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - National Shawmut Bank, 1927-1947, (4 folders) (Box 15, Folder 11-14)
  - William Rockhill Nelson Trust, 1931-1935 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - New Britain, CT, 1926, 1938-1946, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 16-17)
  - F.J. Newcomb Mfg. Co., 1928 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Newcomb-Macklin Co., 1935-1946, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
  - Newhouse Galleries, 1928-1932, (3 folders) (Box 15, Folder 21-23)
  - Newhouse Galleries, 1933-1946, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  - Newport Art Association, 1927-1929, circa 1935-1938, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 3-5)
  - Newton, Arthur U., 1928-1933, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 6-8)
  - Arthur U. Newton Galleries, 1933-1947, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
  - Newspapermen, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - New York Historical Society, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Nichols, Frances, Mrs., 1934-1937 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Nicholson, John, circa 1928-1937, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - John Nicholson Gallery, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - W. & C. Nightingale, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Northern Picture Frame Co., 1939-1946 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Norton, The Misses, 1925-1927 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Norton, R.C., 1937-1938, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Norton, William E. (Estate of), 1921-1933, 1985, (4 folders) (Box 16, Folder 20-23)
  - The Norton Galleries, 1944-1946 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - O File, 1921-1943, 1947, 1993, (6 folders) (Box 16, Folder 25-30)
  - Oberlin College, 1923-1925 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Old Colony Trust Co., 1926-1927 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - The Old Print Shop Inc., 1944-1946 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Omaha, NE, 1931-1933, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Osgood, Elizabeth (and Laura Wright), 1941-1945 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Ottawa, National Gallery of Canada, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - P File, 1922-1932, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 37-38)
  - P File, 1925-1948, 1991, (7 folders) (Box 17, Folder 1-7)
  - Packard Buffalo, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - John S. Packard, Inc., 1931, 1933, 1941-1946 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Paige, David, 1931-1933 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Paine, Nathan, 1945-1946 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - (California) Palace of the Legion of Honor, 1927-1928, 1935-1937, 1947, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
  - Palm Beach Society of the Four Arts, 1936-1937, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Palmer, George S., circa 1917-1921, 1947, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Parker, Woodruff J., 1922-1926, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 16-17)
  - Parmalee, James, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Parsons, Edwin, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Parsons, Harold, 1931-1938 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Fred J. Peters, Inc., 1929 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Philadelphia Art Galleries, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Phillips, Mary E., 1917-1926 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Phillips Memorial Garden, 1926-1927 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Phipps, L.C., Senator, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Pictures Offered, 1927-1928, 1931-1938, (3 folders) (Box 17, Folder 26-28)
  - Pictures Offered to Us, 1919, 1925-1927, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 29-30)
  - Podgoursky, Ivan, Count, 1931-1936 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Potter, Lucius D., Mrs., 1931, 1936, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Price Lists, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Prices, 1928-1929 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Prospective Customers, 1921, 1926-1929, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 35-36)
  - Prospective Customers - Antiques, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - The Providence Journal, 1921-1932, (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Q File, 1926-1939 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Quinn, Charles H., Mrs., 1931-1933, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - R File, 1899-1940, 1947, 1980, 1993, (5 folders) (Box 18, Folder 5-9)
  - Reflectors, 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Rehm, F.K.M. (George Luks Estate), 1924, 1934-1935, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Henry Reinhardt & Son, Inc. [Reinhardt Galleries], 1925-1928 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Reinhardt Galleries, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Reiss, Edward J., 1935-1940 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Rembrandt, 1929-1936, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Restoration, 1926-1929, (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 16-17)
  - Rhode Island Historical Society, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Rhode Island School of Design, 1921-1938, 1947, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 18, Folder 19-21)
  - Rice, Henry W. (Estate of), 1935-1936, 1947, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Rice, Herbert, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Richmond, VA, 1931-1933 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Roberts, William, 1929-1937, 1947, 1995, (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 25-26)
  - Rosen, Maud von, Countess, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Rosenthal, Albert, 1927-1938, 1947, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 18, Folder 28-30)
  - Royar's Framing Shop (Los Angeles, CA), 1929-1938, 1947, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 18, Folder 31-33)
  - Russell, Charles, Mrs., 1928-1933 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - S File, 1914-1925, 1936, 1947, 1995, (4 folders) (Box 18, Folder 35-38)
  - S File, 1925-1929, 1936-1947, 1993, (6 folders) (Box 19, Folder 1-6)
  - St. Louis City Art Museum, 1914-1929, 1934-1938, 1947, 1985, 1991, 1995, (6 folders) (Box 19, Folder 7-12)
  - San Diego Fine Arts Gallery, 1926-1929, 1934-1938, 1947, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 19, Folder 13-15)
  - Sargent, John Singer, 1921-1924 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Savannah, GA, 1937-1938, 1947, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Schultheis, Henry, 1921-1925, 1929, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
  - Schwartz Galleries, 1923, 1925-1929, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 20-21)
  - Scott & Fowles, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - W. Scott & Sons, 1913, 1921-1929, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 23-24)
  - Seachrest, Effie, 1921-1928, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 25-26)
  - Searle, Augustus, Mrs., 1935-1936, 1947, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Laura Davidson Sears Academy of Fine Arts, 1927-1929, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 28-29)
  - Secor, Arthur J., 1922-1925, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Secor, Arthur J., 1926-1939, 1947, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  - Seydel, L. Victor, 1922-1927, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 4-5)
  - Shaw, Edwin, 1922-1924, 1979, 1985, (4 folders) (Box 20, Folder 6-9)
  - Shaw Photo Services, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Sherman, F.F., 1929 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Shortridge Galleries, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Shortridge, Paul, 1924-1926, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
  - Sleeper, Henry D., 1926-1927 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Smaltz, Alfred G., 1929 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Smith College, 1920-1921, 1947, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Smith College (Alfred V. Churchill), 1921-1928 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Springfield Museum of Art, 1935, 1947, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Springfield [MA] Newspapers, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - [Regarding Stuart's "Portrait of Washington" and Gainsborough's "Mrs. Dymock"], 1925, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Stendahl, Earl, 1923-1925, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Stewart, Joseph, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Stimmel, William S., 1917, 1947, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Stock Letters, 1924-1928, 1938, 1995, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 25-26)
  - Stone, Galen L., Mrs., 1928-1929 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Stone & Downer, 1922-1930, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 28-29)
  - Stransky, Josef, 1921-1925, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Strause, Emilie M., 1921-1924, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 31-32)
  - Suzannah and the Elder, 1925-1926 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Swift, James M., 1915-1929, 1947, 1985, 1991, (3 folders) (Box 20, Folder 34-36)
  - T File, 1914, 1921-1947, 1993, 1995, (6 folders) (Box 20, Folder 37-42)
  - Tablets Ordered, 1924-1929 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Tarkington, Booth (Kennebunkport, ME), 1930-1938, 1995, (6 folders) (Box 21, Folder 2-7)
  - Taylor, Charles H., 1910, 1921-1938, 1947, 1985, (3 folders) (Box 21, Folder 8-10)
  - Thayer, Abbott H. (Family of), 1920-1922 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Thompson, D. Croal, 1921-1929, (4 folders) (Box 21, Folder 12-15)
  - Thompson, W.C. (personal), 1929 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - The Thomson Galleries, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Tilden-Thurber Co., 1929 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Tilt, J.E. [Tilt Galleries], 1928-1929 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - The Toledo Museum of Fine Art, 1923-1929, 1939-1945, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 21, Folder 20-22)
  - Arthur Tooth & Sons, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - The Art Gallery of Toronto, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - [Boston Evening] Transcript, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Trebilcock, Paul, 1928-1929 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Troll, Conrad, 1935, 1947, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Twombly, A.S., 1906 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - U File, 1925, 1929, 1939-1940, (3 folders) (Box 21, Folder 29-31)
  - University Club, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - U.S. Printing and Lithograph Company, Joseph Muller, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - V File, 1921-1940, (3 folders) (Box 21, Folder 34-36)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1935-1938, 1947, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Vose Galleries Business, 1928, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Vose Minneapolis, 1929, November - December (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Vose, R.C., Los Angeles Letters, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Vose, R.C., On the Road, 1929, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Vose, R.C., Personal, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - R.C. & N.M. Vose, 1909, 1920-1926, 1985, (3 folders) (Box 22, Folder 2-4)
  - W File, 1921-1929, 1935-1940, 1947, (11 folders) (Box 22, Folder 5-15)
  - Wallick, Frederick, 1934, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Wallis, Henry, 1917-1925, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 22, Folder 17-18)
  - The French Gallery (Wallis & Son), 1913-1915, 1947, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Wallis & Son, 1926-1928 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Washington, D.C. Exhibition (May 1926), 1925-1926 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Waterman, William C. (Estate of), 1923-1924 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Watrous, Harry, 1917-1925, 1937, 1947, 1995, (2 folders) (Box 22, Folder 23-24)
  - Watson, Dawson (Artist), 1923-1925 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Waugh, Frederick J., 1910 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Webster, George H., Mrs., 1937-1938, 1947, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Webster, John Lee, 1919, 1947, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Weir, John (Artist), 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Weiss & Weiss Law Firm [Jablon & Rose], 1933-1938, (3 folders) (Box 22, Folder 30-32)
  - Wetzell, Lester, 1921-1925, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - White, R.H., 1915-1916, 1947, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Wiegand, Gustave, 1934-1938, 1947, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Wildenstein & Co., 1922-1942, 1947, 1995, (2 folders) (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
  - Williams & Sutch [The United Arts Gallery], 1921-1925 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - E.J. van Wisselingh & Co., 1935-1936, 1947, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Woodruff Brothers, 1923-1925 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Worchester Art Museum, 1923-1925 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - X-Y-Z File, 1938-1940, 1947, (2 folders) (Box 23, Folder 11-12)
  - Y File, 1921-1928 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Howard Young Galleries, 1922-1938, 1947, 1995, (4 folders) (Box 23, Folder 14-17)
  - Yunt Art Galleries, 1922-1924 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - S.M. Yunt [Yunt Art Galleries], 1926-1928 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Z File, 1923-1928 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Zug, George B., 1911, 1921-1927 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Zuloaga, Ignacio, 1924-1925 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Customer Files, 1912-1946, Series 2:; (Boxes 23-24; 0.8 linear feet)
  Customer Files appear to be materials compiled by Vose Galleries about potential customer contacts in preparation for business travel to cities throughout the United States. Materials include lists of potential clients, notes, correspondence, and scattered museum catalogs.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by geographic location; however, there are a handful of folder titles by subject.
  - Akron, OH, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Atlanta, GA, circa 1930s-1941 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Australia, 1933-1934 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Brockton, MA, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Charlotte, NC, circa 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Chicago, IL, 1920s-1930s (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Cincinnati, OH, circa 1933-1934 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - (Some) Connecticut Cities, circa 1920s-1930s (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Dallas, TX, 1921-1937 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Denver, CO, circa 1920s-1930s (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Des Moines, IA, 1933 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Detroit, MI, 1925-1940 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - El Paso, TX, undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Fort Wayne, IN, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Fort Worth, TX, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Grand Rapids, MI, 1927, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Hartford, CT, 1930s (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Holyoke, MA, 1928, undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Houston, TX, 1920s-1930s (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Indianapolis, IN, circa 1933-1934 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Kansas City, MO, circa 1927-1929 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Maine, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Malden, MA, 1932-1934 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Manchester, NH, 1933 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Massachusetts Artists, undated (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Memphis, TN, 1920s-1930s, undated (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Milwaukee, WI, 1920s-1930s (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Minneapolis, MN, 1912-1930s (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Museum Directors, 1930s (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Nashville, TN, 1941-1944 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Newport, RI, circa 1920s-1940s (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Omaha, NE, 1937, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Palm Beach, FL, 1936-1937 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Philadelphia, PA, circa 1920s-1930s (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Ponca City, OK, 1931 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Providence, RI, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Richmond, VA, circa 1930s (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Rochester, NY, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - St. Louis, MO and Toledo, OH, 1927-1936 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - St. Paul, MN, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Seattle, WA, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Special Lists, All on Cards, 1935-1946 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Springfield, MA, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Springville, UT, 1929, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Syracuse, NY, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Toronto, Ontario, 1920s-1930s (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Tucson, AZ, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Tulsa, OK, circa 1926-1937 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Utica, NY, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Warren, OH, undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Washington, D.C., 1921 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Wealthiest and Most Prominent Art Collectors in the U.S., 1921 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Williamsport, PA, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Wilmington, DE, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Youngstown, OH, circa 1921-1933 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Art-Related Files, circa 1876, 1890s-1947, Series 3:; (Box 24; 7 folders)